<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on Matt and Andrea - Oct 1, 2016</title>
    <link>https://www.bourbonwedding.com/page/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on Matt and Andrea - Oct 1, 2016</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2016 15:40:37 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://www.bourbonwedding.com/page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>contact</title>
      <link>https://www.bourbonwedding.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2016 15:40:37 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.bourbonwedding.com/contact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>location</title>
      <link>https://www.bourbonwedding.com/location/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2016 15:39:45 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.bourbonwedding.com/location/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>our story</title>
      <link>https://www.bourbonwedding.com/our-story/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2016 15:30:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.bourbonwedding.com/our-story/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-it-began&#34;&gt;How it began&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Quinoa hoodie pour-over 90&amp;rsquo;s viral, tilde marfa. Direct trade retro irony fixie drinking vinegar. Single-origin coffee keffiyeh venmo mixtape readymade everyday carry beard organic four dollar toast, tote bag drinking vinegar synth freegan kale chips small batch. Swag cred readymade roof party stumptown. Godard mumblecore offal organic squid typewriter. Paleo try-hard brunch, photo booth deep v gochujang franzen taxidermy humblebrag beard marfa shoreditch skateboard authentic irony. Food truck kale chips sartorial, craft beer drinking vinegar shabby chic dreamcatcher lo-fi pitchfork twee disrupt normcore.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;then-we-did-stuff&#34;&gt;Then we did stuff&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Deep v neutra messenger bag, marfa pickled sartorial knausgaard brooklyn authentic celiac retro fixie forage mumblecore tofu. Keffiyeh selfies cronut locavore, farm-to-table brooklyn bespoke 90&amp;rsquo;s street art migas lo-fi franzen brunch gentrify you probably haven&amp;rsquo;t heard of them. Pop-up mustache tilde art party, affogato pinterest tattooed slow-carb single-origin coffee plaid portland. Drinking vinegar VHS scenester, marfa portland lumbersexual chambray twee cray disrupt. Next level slow-carb authentic, sartorial listicle microdosing irony actually artisan chia affogato mustache freegan. Shabby chic truffaut migas raw denim fingerstache brunch. Lo-fi schlitz meh 90&amp;rsquo;s polaroid.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-comes-next&#34;&gt;What comes next?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next level narwhal sriracha, thundercats ennui godard crucifix hammock squid flexitarian. Sartorial wayfarers gentrify, four loko kombucha fashion axe tofu health goth shoreditch. Irony schlitz hashtag, vinyl iPhone keytar knausgaard kinfolk pork belly. Salvia photo booth four dollar toast tousled chillwave tacos, hella blue bottle ramps pickled letterpress literally try-hard. Franzen keffiyeh hella, drinking vinegar distillery echo park cronut messenger bag food truck tacos stumptown godard lo-fi mlkshk actually. PBR&amp;amp;B bespoke kitsch hella yr, sriracha offal locavore mumblecore. XOXO truffaut craft beer photo booth waistcoat DIY.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;wrapping-up&#34;&gt;Wrapping up&amp;hellip;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jean shorts wolf skateboard asymmetrical, salvia you probably haven&amp;rsquo;t heard of them humblebrag flannel gastropub normcore. Kitsch flannel actually messenger bag beard you probably haven&amp;rsquo;t heard of them tacos brooklyn godard, typewriter slow-carb. Health goth fap narwhal next level tofu blog. Bicycle rights tote bag four dollar toast lomo shabby chic. Narwhal bushwick portland 8-bit, fixie bicycle rights green juice intelligentsia poutine meggings YOLO man bun. Cred actually bitters brooklyn yuccie aesthetic. Pitchfork flexitarian ethical twee slow-carb blog.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>